export default [
    {
      question:
        "What instrument does Phoebe play?",
      answer: "Guitar",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "easy"
    },
    {
      question: "Which one of Joey's sisters did Chandler hook up with?",
      answer: "Mary Angela",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "medium"
    },
    {
      question:
        "What does Monica Geller do for a living?",
      answer: "She's a chef",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "easy"
    },
    {
      question: "What is Chandler Bing's middle name?",
      answer: "Muriel",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "hard"
    },
    {
      question: "What does Phoebe for for her brother Frank Jr and his wife?",
      answer: "Have their baby",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "medium"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of Ross' first wife?",
      answer: "Carol",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "easy"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the nickname Monica's dad gives her?",
      answer: "Little Harmonica",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "hard"
    },
    {
      question: "Monica categorizes her towels...how many categories are there?",
      answer: "Eleven",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "hard"
    },
    {
      question:
        "How many sisters does Joey Tribbiani have?",
      answer: "Seven",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "medium"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the person they watch through the window?",
      answer: "Ugly Naked Guy",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "easy"
    },
    {
      question: "What is Joey's agent's name?",
      answer: "Estelle",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "easy"
    },
    {
      question: "After Richard and Monica break up, what does Monica become obsessed with?",
      answer: "Making jam",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "hard"
    },
    {
      question:
        "What kind of stuffed animal does Joey sleep with?",
      answer: "A penguin",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "hard"
    },
    {
      question: 'Which character said the memorable line, "Pivot"?',
      answer: "Ross",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "medium"
    },
    {
      question: "What is Chandler's father's job?",
      answer: "A drag queen in Vegas",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "medium"
    },
    {
      question: "What name does Ross say at his wedding?",
      answer: "Rachel",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "medium"
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the phrase that Joey Tribbiani is famous for?",
      answer: "How you doin'?",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "easy"
    },
    {
      question: "What sport do the friends play on Thanksgiving?",
      answer: "Football",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "easy"
    },
    {
      question: "Who did Phoebe think her grandfather was?",
      answer: "Albert Einstein",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "medium"
    },
    {
      question: "For a while, Ross owns a pet monkey named Marcel. What happened to him?",
      answer: "Ross gives him away to a zoo, and Marcel then becomes a movie star.",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "medium"
    },
    {
      question: "Chandler falls asleep during a work meeting and accidentally agrees to move to which city/state?",
      answer: "Tulsa, OK",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "hard"
    },
    {
      question: "Which show do Chandler and Joey bond over when they first move in together?",
      answer: "Baywatch",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "medium"
    },
    {
      question: "What color are the kitchen cabinets in Monica's apartment?",
      answer: "Blue",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "easy"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the white-haired barista?",
      answer: "Gunther",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "medium"
    },
    {
      question: "Phoebe Buffay has a twin. What’s her name?",
      answer: "Ursula",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "easy"
    },
    {
      question: "How was Joey’s character written off on Days Of Our Lives?",
      answer: "He falls down an elevator shaft",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "hard"
    },
    {
      question: "During one of the Christmas episodes, Ross entertains his son Ben by dressing up as...?",
      answer: "The Holiday Armadillo",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "hard"
    },
    {
      question: "Where did Monica and Chandler first get together?",
      answer: "In London, at Ross' wedding",
      answerShown: false,
      difficulty: "medium"
    }
  ].map((q, index) => ({ ...q, id: index + 1 }));;